Shrouq Ramadan Saad

Email: shrougramadan8@gmail.com

Phone: +20 102 147 9716

Summary

Hello there, my name is Shrouq Ramadan, I'm a React.js Frontend Web Developer who has 2+ Years of work experience in industry of frontend web development, I enjoy building everything with JavaScript.

In this duration, I have learned a lot of technologies, created many cool websites, Collaborated with great developers and contributed to open-source projects.

So, I'm always seeking to have an opportunity that matches my skills, to make the Best use of all what I have learned

Work Experience / Internships

Node JS and Angular Course

(Mar 2023 – Apr 2023)

• At National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

• Front End Developer Intern

(Aug 2022 - Dec 2022)

- At ROUTE ACADEMY
- The role includes using API With react & native JavaScript

Front End Developer Intern

(Sep 2022)

- At National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)
- The role includes web design.
- Final Project result :98%

Full Stack developer engineer

(Feb 2022 – Jun 2022)

- At CMark Company, Egypt branch
- The role includes front-end development and PHP Laravel backend development

Full stack Developer Intern

(Jul 2021 - Jan 2022)

At INSTANT ACADEMY

Education

2016 – 2021 Bachelor of Science Information system, Faculty of

Information Technology, Misr University for Science and technology (MUST), EGYPT.

Graduation project: Website Car Turning. Graduation Project Degree: Distinction

Skills

- Technical Skills
 - React JS
 - JavaScript /Typescript
 - **OECMASCRIPT 6**
 - ojQuery
 - OHTML5
 - oCSS3
 - Bootstrap 5
 - Object-oriented programming
 - Adobe XD
 - Git/GitHub
 - Node JS
 - Angular JS
- Interpersonal Skills
 - Self-learner.
 - Work under pressure.
- Languages

Arabic : Native.

English : Conversation.

○ German : Beginner

Personal Information

• LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/shroug-ramadan-a84289202/

• **GitHub**: https://github.com/ShrouqRamadan